{
    "id": "69c6d662096f499fbd7dc97632138605",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………… be there before 8 o’clock. (compulsion)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "would",
                "ought",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you lend me a few dollars? (polite request)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. not have done this to me. (criticism)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………. be driving now. (probability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………. rain in the evening. (weak possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… not have waited for them. (lack of necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "can",
                "may",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I wait any longer? (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Need",
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… to follow traffic rules. (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I turn the heating on? (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Need",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………….. have helped me. Why did you just sit and watch? (criticism)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}